Top three steps of showing love,
الخطوة الثالثة من طريقة التعبير عن الحب
the drunk test method.
طريقة الاختبار بعد السكر
Wine is the best catalyst that promotes emotional communication
الخمر هو تعزيز التواصل العاطفي
and makes someone drunk and...
لإثارة الفوضى بعد الشرب
reveals his true feelings.
أفضل مضاد لإظهار الحقيقة
Anyway,
على أي حال
according to incomplete statistics,
حسب الإحصاء غير كامل
confessing and being confessed
الاعتراف والاعتراف
usually happen after someone is drunk.
بعد أن ثملت
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل
Mr. Liu, this looks more real.
سيد ليو هذا يبدو أكثر واقعية
Right?
أليس كذلك
Let's make a bet.
دعنا نراهن
when you are drunk?
بعد أن ثملت
Assistant Tang.
‫المساعد تانغ‬
You can leave now.
‫يمكنك الانسحاب‬
Roger.
عُلم
Hello?
ألو مرحبا
Hello.
مرحبا
Is Miss Tian Tian speaking?
هل أنت الآنسة تيان تيان
Mr. Liu is drunk here.
السيد ليو ثمل هنا
Can you come and pick him up?
هل يمكنك أن تأتي لاستقباله؟
Yes, but...
ممكن لكن
Okay, I'll send you the address.
حسنا سأرسل لك العنوان
He... Hello?
ألو ألو لا
Hey!
ألو
What the heck?
هل هذا خطأ
You asked me to pick you up so late.
‫طلب مني أن آخذه في هذا الوقت المتأخر‬
Is Assistant Tang on strike?
هل قام المساعد تانغ بإيقاف العمل
Mr. Liu, you...
المدير ليو أنت
Mr. Liu.
المدير ليو
You...
أنت
Mr. Liu, why are you so drunk?
المدير ليو لماذا أنت سكران هكذا
Mr. Liu.
المدير ليو
Assistant Tian.
مساعدة تيان
I don't want to go home.
لا أريد العودة إلى المنزل
My house is too empty.
المنزل فارغ جدا
No one accompanies me.
لا أحد يرافقني
Don't force yourself if you can't drink.
لا تجبر على الشرب
You are so drunk at this time.
شربت هكذا في منتصف الليل
Isn't it comfy to stay in?
ألا طعم الفراش في المنزل شهي
Slow down.
ببطء ببطء
Hang in there.
تماسكي
You can never wake me up, now that I'm pretending to be drunk.
لن تستيقظني أبدا
Gosh, it's lucky that it's me.
‫يا إلهي لحسن الحظ أنا‬
If she was someone younger,
إذا غيرت فتاة ضعيفة القوة
she would've dragged you back.
ربما سوف تسحبك على الأرض
It hurts.
هذا مؤلم
I didn't expect that
لم أتوقع
Assistant Tian is so enthusiastic.
أن الآنسة تيان متحمسة جدا
She even gave me a wall bam.
كيف يمكن أن يصمد علي
So,
الآن
is she going to confess her love?
هل ستعترف بحبه
His eyebrows are so pretty.
حاجبيه جميل جدا
Why is his skin so delicate?
لماذا بشرته رقيق هكذا؟
And his lips.
والشفاه
How does his lips look like jelly?
لماذا تبدو مثل البرد؟
What am I thinking?
ما الذي أفكر به؟
It's time to go.
سأذهب
They're almost there.
بقي خطوة واحدة فقط
Did Assistant Tian run away
لا يمكن أن تكون السيدة تيان خجولة
because she's shy?
بسبب خجل
Assistant Tian.
مساعدة تيان
Please work harder!
ابذلي قصارى جهدك
You said I have bad sleeping habits.
وقالت إن نومي ضعيف
I just made a glass of honey water
أخذت كوبا من الماء العسل
and you fell asleep on the floor.
وأنت نمت على الأرض
Mr. Liu.
المدير ليو
Wake up.
استيقظ
You're sleeping on the floor.
لقد نمت على الأرض
Mr. Liu.
المدير ليو
This is a honey water.
هذا ماء العسل
Drink this to sober up.
اشربي رشفة لتستيقظ من الكحول
Assistant Tian.
آنسة تيان
You seem to have something to tell me.
يبدو أنك تريد التحدث معي
Go ahead.
تكلم
I'll promise you anything.
أعدك بكل شيء
Are you serious, Mr. Liu?
هل أنت جاد أيها المدير ليو
Come on, baby.
هيا يا حبيبتي
Here's the thing.
هكذا
You've recovered.
لقد تعافيت
I am not an assistant to you anymore,
بالنسبة لك
Of course.
بالطبع
To me,
بالنسبة لي
you're no longer an assistant.
أنت لست مساعدًا منذ فترة طويلة
Then, can you please
هل يمكنني
not summon me
في المستقبل
as your assistant in future?
إلى جانبك
Sure.
ممكن
Go ahead.
أخبرني
I'll promise you
أي هوية تريد أن تغيرها
whatever identity you want to change.
أعدك
Come on.
هيا
That's great.
هذا رائع
I hope that
أتمنى
during my free time,
وقت الفراغ
I can have more
يمكنني الحصول على المزيد من
freedom.
الحرية
Sure.
ممكن
After all, I am a CEO that respects employees
بعد كل شيء أنا مدير يحترم الموظفين
to have their own free time.
وموظفي
Since I took care of you
بالنظر إلى الليلة
until midnight,
سأعتني بك حتى منتصف الليل
can I take a half day off tomorrow?
هل يمكنني أخذ استراحة نصف يوم غدًا؟
Sure.
حسنا
Thank you, Mr. Liu.
شكراً لك سيد ليو
I'll go back now.
سأعود الآن
Are you leaving now?
هل ستغادر الآن؟
Yes, it's very late now.
لقد تأخر الوقت
Tomorrow is coming.
غدًا قريبًا
Can I take leave now?
هل يمكنني إجازة
Bye.
مع السلامة
Assistant Tian,
مساعدة تيان
thank you for taking care of me tonight.
شكرا على رعايتك الليلة
No.
لا
I can't call you Assistant Tian anymore.
لا يمكنني أن أناديك بالسيد تيان الآن
I should call you Designer Tian.
يمكنني فقط أن أناديك المصممة تيان
But it's a bit awkward to call you that.
‫لكن هذا غير مناسب
Since
من أجل إظهار
we used to be close partners,
أننا كنا شريكين مقربين
I can call you Tian
يمكنني أن أناديك بالسيان
or Sweetie Tian.
أو تيان تيان
Choose one.
اختاري واحدة
Tian.
تيان
Sweetie Tian.
تيان تيان
Good night, Tian.
ليلة سعيدة يا تيان
What the hell?
ما هذا
Tian.
تيان
You didn't sleep well last night, did you?
ألم تنم جيدا أمس
You even have dark circles under your eyes.
لديك دائرة سوداء
Do you want a piece of facial mask?
هل تريد أن تضع قطعة أيضًا؟
Wait.
انتظر
What did you call me?
ماذا ناديتني للتو
Tian.
تيان
Huh?
غريب
I don't think it's cheesy.
لا أشعر بالغثيان
Rose.
رقيق
Say it again.
مرة أخرى
You're not yourself today.
أنت غير طبيعي اليوم
What happened? Tell me the truth.
ماذا حدث؟ أخبرني الحقيقة
I...
أنا
I think
أعتقد
Mr. Liu likes me.
المدير ليو يحبني
You finally switched to
لقد غيرت أخيرا
our romance novel channel.
قناة روايتنا الرومانسية
This must be the story that a weirdo boss
يجب أن يكون هذا
falls in love with me, right?
وقعت في حبي
It's not a plot. It's reality.
ليست قصة بل الحقيقة
Rose, look.
أنظري
I work outstation.
ذهبت للعمل
He followed me there
كان يتبعني خصيصًا
and had dinner with me.
ويرافقني لتناول الطعام
He was afraid that you would slack off
يخشى أن تتكاسل
so he's always watching you.
لذلك يراقبك طوال الوقت
The brutal chief editor is the same.
رئيس التحرير القاتلة مثلي أيضًا
He got drunk and called me.
كان ثملاً اتصل بي
He asked me to pick him up and take care of him.
وطلب مني أن آخذه وأعتني به
He's treating you
إنه يعاملك كموظفة بار 24 عامًا
as a loyal employee.
أليس كذلك
He always used my position as special assistant as an excuse
‫فهو دائمًا يستخدم مساعد خاص كعذر‬
to ask me to work with him
طلب مني أن أكون معه
so he can get close to me, right?
من أجل الاقتراب مني
Are you being mind controlled?
هل أنت تحت السيطرة الروحي؟
It's obviously exploiting your remaining labor force.
من الواضح أنك تضغط على باقي العمال
Well,
إذا
he gave breakfast to all the employees.
أرسل الفطور إلى جميع المكتب
But for me,
إلا أنا
he gave me human-shaped signboard and photos too.
هناك بطاقة شكله الإنساني والكتابة
Sister, he's a weirdo.
يا أختي إنه غريب
Based on my experience,
حسب خبرتي
you'll be boycotted
أنت فقط تنتظر
by your aggrieved colleagues.
من زملائك غير عادلون
Then he called me Tian
إذا كان يناديني آتيان
just for convenience?
هل هو حقا من أجل الصراخ
Sister,
أختي
don't blame me for not reminding you.
لا تلومني على عدم تذكيرك
There are three delusions in life.
الحياة في الحياة، ثلاثة وهم
First,
أولا
mobile vibration.
الهاتف يهتز
Second,
ثانياً
I can fight back.
يمكنني قتله
Third,
ثالثاً
he likes me.
إنه يحبني
I must be thinking too much.
لقد فكرت كثيراً
Hello, who is this?
مرحبًا، من هذا؟
Junior, it's me.
إنها أنا
Senior Luo Ci.
لو سي
The Stray Animals charity event
كنز ضال في صندوق دا فو
organized by Dafu Public Welfare Fund has started.
بدأ المشروع الخيري
I need someone to help me.
أريد أن أجد شخص للمساعدة
Would you come over?
هل تريد أن تأتي للمساعدة
Yes, I do. I am willing to work for charity.
نعم نعم
Okay.
حسنا
For this charity event,
هذا النشاط الخيري
you agreed without hesitation.
وافقت دون تردد
You're the junior that I am looking up to.
إنها الزميلة التي أحبها
Senior.
أيها الزميل الأكبر
Everyone is responsible for the charity event.
كل شخص مسؤول عن الأنشطة الخيرية
Moreover,
علاوة على ذلك
I am happy to work with you
العمل مع الزميل الأكبر
and I learn a lot at the same time.
‫وسعيدة ومعرفة الكثير من الأشياء‬
This time,
هذه المرة
besides publishing brochures
باستثناء إعطاء
for the Shelter of Stray Animals,
في منزل الأطفال الضالة
I want to design some toys for my the strays.
أريد تصميم بعض الألعاب للأطفال
Look.
انظر
This is
هذا
a blueprint for cat climbing frame.
تصميم تسلق القط
I want to build this climbing frame outside.
أريد بناء هذه القطط خارج الغرفة
If you have any good ideas,
إذا كان لديك أي فكرة جيدة
you can add it directly.
يمكنك إضافتها مباشرة
Really?
‫ممكن؟‬
Thank you senior.
‫شكراً لك أيها الموجه‬
I think this
‫أعتقد أن هنا‬
can be changed slightly
يمكن أن تتغير قليلا
by making it more secretive.
‫يمكن زيادة بعض الإحساس الخفية‬
Senior.
أيها الزميل الأكبر
How about this?
ما رأيك بهذا؟
Most stray animals
الحيوانات الضالة
are insecure.
معظمهم لا يشعرون بالأمان
Therefore, we should change the cat house to a closed one.
لذلك غيرت غرفة القطط إلى طريقة مغلقة
It can protect them from the sun and rain
يمكن أن تغطي الشمس والمطر لهم
and make them feel safe.
ويمكن أن يجعلهم يشعرون بالأمان
Good.
جيد
You are very imaginative and sympathetic.
‫الزميلة لديها خيال وفي نفس الفكرة‬
You have a kind heart too.
‫الزميل الأكبر لديه قلب طيب أيضا‬
Sorry, senior.
أنا آسفة
I have to take this.
سأجيب على الهاتف
Tian.
تيان
Can I invite you
مساء الغد
to have dinner together tomorrow night?
هل يمكنني دعوتك لتناول العشاء معا
Sorry, Mr. Liu.
آسف سيد ليو
I have plans tomorrow.
لدي خطة غدا
Let's meet another day.
لنتقابل في يوم آخر
Okay.
‫حسنا‬
Assistant Tang,
‫المساعد تانغ‬
Didn't you say
ألم تقل
from opening to closing my eyes,
منذ فتح عيني حتى أغمض عيني
I've already,
‫في جميع الاتجاهات‬
at 360 degrees without dead angle,
360 درجة بدون زاوية الموت
warmed Tian?
هل دافئ دان
Then, why did Tian
لماذا تيان
refuse me so coldly?
رفضني بدون درجة الحرارة
Why didn't you tell her directly that
لماذا لم تخبرها مباشرة
you booked a restaurant
أنك حجزت مطعم
and prepared candlelight dinner for her?
أعددت لها عشاء ضوء الشموع
We should keep our word.
يجب أن تكون مخلصا
I've agreed
لقد اتفقنا
not to occupy her time by force.
لن أستغل وقتها مرة أخرى
How can I kidnap her morally?
كيف يمكن الاختطاف الأخلاقي
Mr. Liu, you're getting more and more considerate.
المدير ليو أنت أكثر فأكثر تفهم الآخرين
I have an idea too.
لدي فكرة أيضا
Can you
هل يمكنك
be nicer to me too?
تعاملني بشكل أفضل
Assistant Tang,
‫مساعد تانغ‬
I've been so nice to you
لقد عاملتك بشكل جيد
that you're asking me for this.
بدأت تطلبين هذا الطلب لي
Just another day of losing to Assistant Tian.
لا تزال لا تستطيع مقارنة بالمساعدة تيان
It is weekend tomorrow.
غدا نهاية الأسبوع
Is there anything
إذا كان هناك أي شيء
more interesting than being with me?
أكثر إثارة للاهتمام من مرافقتي
It must be a natural disaster
هذا بالتأكيد كارثة طبيعية
which she can't get out of it.
لا يمكن الهروب
Otherwise, nothing is more interesting
وإلا لن يكون هناك شيء أكثر إثارة للاهتمام
than being with you.
أكثر إثارة للاهتمام
If this word
إذا كانت هذه الجملة
comes out from Tian's mouth,
من فم دان
I think it'll be more pleasant.
أعتقد أنه سيكون أكثر سعادة
Well, this weekend,
في نهاية هذا الأسبوع
Why don't you stay home and rest?
من الأفضل أن ترتاح في المنزل
No.
لا
The whole world is in involution.
العالم كله في الداخل
How can I slack off?
كيف يمكنني الاسترخاء
I'm going to make sure that my weekend schedule is full.
رتبت عطلة نهاية الأسبوع بشكل كامل
Okay.
حسنا
I guess my weekend is ruined again.
يبدو أن هذا الأسبوع قد فشلت مرة أخرى
Why do I always get hurt?
لماذا أصبت دائما
Here's the order details.
هذه هي تفاصيل الطلب
Please sign here.
وقع عليها
Boss, I want to check the goods.
سيدي أريد التحقق من البضائع
Okay, look. These are all good stuff.
حسنًا، انظر، جميعها أشياء جيدة
Look.
انظر
Boss,
سيدي
we ordered oak.
طلبنا "الممو".
This box is not oak, right?
هل هذا الصندوق صحيح؟
No.
لا
Look at this box.
انظر إلى هذا الصندوق
It's so similar.
إنه يشبه
It's not about whether they look alike or not.
ليست مشكلة مشابهة أم لا
It's about whether they are or not.
بل المشكلة
Miss.
يا فتاة
Look at the color and pattern.
انظر إلى هذا اللون والخط
They are all good wood.
كلها خشب جيد
They are very strong.
قوية جدا
Sir.
سيدي
Oak guards against insects.
"مومو" منع الحشرات"
This piece of wood
أيها الخشب
will break easily after being blown by wind and rain.
من السهل قطع الرياح والمطر
Miss.
يا فتاة
The wood in our factory
الخشب في مصنعنا
is very strong.
قوية جدا
People can't even break them,
لا يمكن قطع الناس
not to mention cats.
ناهيك عن القطط
Don't take it too seriously.
لا تكوني جادة
They're almost the same.
كل شيء على ما يرام
If you say so,
إذا قلت ذلك حقًا
I'll take it seriously.
سأكون جادة
Didn't you say that it couldn't be broken?
ألم تقل لا يمكن قطعها
If you can break them,
إذا استطعت قطعه
I'll change them for you.
سأغير لك دون قول أي شيء
Sir, can you fulfill your promise?
سيدي هل يمكنك الوفاء بوعدك
Sure, young lady.
حسنًا حسنًا أيتها الفتاة الصغيرة
I'll change the goods for you
سأحضر لك البضائع
with the new ones.
سأغير لك
That's more like it.
هذا أفضل
Senior, when did you come?
متى أتيت يا أخي
What a coincidence.
يا لها من صدفة
I came here just now
عندما
when you broke the wood.
‫عند قطعة الخشب‬
No, senior, let me explain.
لا أيها الزميل الأكبر اسمعني
I am
أنا شخصيتي
a little bit rough.
قليلًا
But it was just violence.
لكنني كنت عنيفة العدالة
Just violence?
العنف العدالة
You can always give me
أنت دائما تعطيني
unexpected surprise.
مفاجأة مفاجئة
I'm relieved that you are not scared.
لا تخيفني
Just violence...
العنف العدالة
It's quite cute.
‫لطيفة جدا‬
Junior.
‫يا زميلتي‬
Watch out!
انتبهي
Tian.
تيان
You need to be careful.
انتبهي لسلامتك
Mr. Liu, why are you here?
المدير ليو لماذا أنت هنا
I was going to ask you too.
أريد أن أسألك
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا
I...
أنا
I asked her to come.
طلبت من زميلتي المجيء
Tian didn't respond to me.
لم ترد دان علي
Is it because of his intervention?
هل هذا بسبب التدخل
Mr. Liu, you're here.
المدير ليو لقد أتيت
Mr. Luo and Miss Tian are here too.
السيد لوه والسيدة شوي لي هنا أيضاً
Let me introduce to you.
دعني أقدم لكم
This is the CEO of Qiansheng Group, Mr. Liu.
هذا المدير ليو من مجموعة شيان شينغ
He's the sponsor of the Shelther of Stray Animals.
هو دعم عائلتنا المتشردة
I specially invited Mr. Liu
لقد دعوت المدير ليو خصيصًا
to attend our launching ceremony today.
لحضور حفل افتتاح اليوم
Mr. Liu, look.
سيد ليو انظر
This is the natural game park
هذا هو تصميم السيد لوه والسيدة شوي لي
designed and built together
مع السيد لوه والسيدة شوي
by Mr. Luo and Miss Tian
لقد قاموا ببناء الملاهي الطبيعية
for their beloved cats.
من أجل قطة
I can feel the overflowing love
لقد شعرت بالفعل
of the creator.
مليئة بالحب
Mr. Liu is so enthusiastic about pet welfare.
المدير ليو يهتم بمصالح الحيوانات الأليفة
I think you must like animals very much.
أعتقد أنه بالتأكيد يحب الحيوانات الصغيرة
Give it a hug. It's cute.
تعانقني إنها لطيفة جدا
Assistant Tian.
مساعدة تيان
Curator Fang.
أيها المدير فانغ
The media should be here in an hour.
يجب أن تصل وسائل الإعلام بعد ساعة
What else do we need to prepare?
هل علينا أن نستعد أي شيء آخر؟
The boss is afraid of cats?
هذا الرئيس يخاف القطط
Why are you laughing?
لماذا تضحك؟
Give it to me.
أعطني إياه
By the way, Mr. Liu,
بالمناسبة سيد ليو
there are so many things waiting for your decision
مجموعة شيان شينغ
in Qiansheng Group.
الكثير من الأشياء تنتظرك لتقرر
Why do you have time
لماذا حفل افتتاح خيري صغير كهذا
to come for a small public welfare launching ceremony?
لديك الوقت لتأتي بنفسك
There's no difference in public welfare.
الخير لا ينقسم الحجم والحجم
Do you think that
هل تعتقد
I can't participate in public welfare
أنني لا أستطيع
like Luo Ci?
مثل لوه سي؟
No.
لا
It's mainly because
السبب الرئيسي هو
this event was initiated by senior.
هذا النشاط من قبل الزميل الأكبر
When we were in Shanshui Village,
في قرية شان شوي
I was worried because you two are not getting along.
كنت قلقاً
He started...
هو
I...
أنا
develop.
في هذا المجال
In this public welfare,
في هذه الصناعة
we
نحن
are equally important.
مهمة نفس الشيء
Besides, I play an important role
إضافة إلى ذلك، تنظيم صندوق دا فو
in the funding of
أنا
Dafu Fund.
لا يمكن أن ينقصني
You can't say that.
لا يمكن قول ذلك
If senior Luo Ci weren't here,
لولا لو سي
we would have neither paid attention to stray animals
قد لا نتابع الحيوانات الضالة
nor Dafu Fund.
ولا يوجد صندوق دا فو
Why do you always speak for him?
لماذا تتحدث نيابة عنه دائما
I think I heard my name.
يبدو أنني سمعت اسمي
Is there anything I can help with?
هل تحتاج إلى مساعدتي؟
Senior, are you done with your work?
هل انتهيت من عملك؟
It's alright.
لا داعي
I'll do it.
يمكنني فعلها
I cooperated very well with Tian just now.
لقد تعاونت مع دان بشكل جيد
Fine.
حسنا
You do it.
تعال
It doesn't matter.
من يأتي مختلف
Assistant Tian.
مساعدة تيان
Mr. Liu.
المدير ليو
You never hug any animals, do you?
ألم تحضن الحيوانات الصغيرة من قبل
I...
أنا
don't like the soft touch.
لا أحب هذا الشعور الناعم
It makes people
يجعل الناس يشعرون
feel fragile.
ضعيف جدا
It's actually very healing.
‫في الواقع يتعافى‬
Why don't you try touching it?
هل تريد أن تجرب
Just a try.
جربي
Just give it a touch.
‫فقط لمس‬
No.
لا
Try it. Try it.
‫جرب جرب جرب‬
Come on.
هيا هيا
How is it?
كيف
It took the initiative to rub you with its head.
إنها تستخدم رأسها لمسك
It means that the cat likes you very much.
هذا يعني أن القطة تحبك كثيرا
They feel at ease and happy in your hands.
أشعر بالراحة والسعادة في يدك
Mr. Liu.
المدير ليو
Why don't you give it a hug?
ما رأيك أن تعانقني
Give it a hug.
عانقيني عانقيني عانقيني
Just one hug.
‫مرة واحدة فقط‬
It is said that this cat
يقال أن هذه القطة الصغيرة
was injured when being saved.
أصيب في جسمه عندما تم إنقاذه
Therefore, it felt insecure.
لا أشعر بالأمان
I tried a few times
لقد حاولت عدة مرات
to win its trust.
حتى أحصل على ثقتها
I didn't expect you to succeed at the first time.
لم أتوقع أنك نجحت في المرة الأولى
Then...
إذًا
this little guy
هذا الشاب
has quite a good taste.
لديه ذوق جيد
Is Tian going to take initiative
هل تريد دان أن تتبادل
to have intimate physical contact with me?
لمس جسدي
Mr. Liu
المدير ليو
♫Love is slowly spreading in our hearts♫
إنها العطر الذي رش اليوم
It smells like mint. ♫Love is slowly spreading in our hearts♫
هناك رائحة النعناع المفضلة للقط
I see.
هكذا
Tian always gives me
يمكن لجيان دائما أن تعطيني بعض الشجاعة
the courage to move forward.
شجاعة للأمام
Seeing her smile so happily ♫The color engraved in my heart♫
عندما رأيتها تبتسم بسعادة
My heart also bursts with joy. ♫Your gentle eyes are staring at our future♫
قلبي يطلق الألعاب النارية أيضا
Loving animals,
وأهتم بالحيوانات الصغيرة
giving love
من أجل الضعفاء
might be a trivial matter
هذا أمر صغير
to each of us.
أمر صغير
But for them,
لكن بالنسبة لهم
it can change their lives.
يمكن تغيير الحياة
Therefore, I hereby call on everyone
لذلك أنا هنا أطلب من الجميع
to use your free time
استغلال وقت الفراغ
to take part in volunteerism ♫Your beautiful smile wipes out my haze♫
كمتطوعة
as a volunteer.
في الأنشطة الخيرية
Here,
هنا
we can get close to cute animals
يمكننا التواصل مع حبيبتنا القريبة
and have a fulfilling
ونقضى فترة كاملة
and meaningful time.
ومفائلة
Thank you.
شكراً لكم جميعاً
Great!
‫حسنا حسنا‬
Assistant Tang.
‫المساعد تانغ‬
This photo
هذه الصورة
is pretty good.
في هذه الصورة
Mr. Liu,
المدير ليو
I'm using the golden ratio
أنا أستخدم نسبة قطع الذهب
to take a sunny and passionate picture
تصوير لك أشعة الشمس والحماس
with you and nature.
الحب الطبيعي بين الناس
You've improved again.
لقد تحسنت مرة أخرى
In this round,
هذه الجولة
human
الطفل البشري
has successfully seized the territory of Cat Planet natives.
نجح في الاستيلاء على تشكيل مياو شينغ
The boss of the altar has fallen to compete with cats.
الرئيس التنفيذي قد وقع في منافسة القط
How is it, Tian?
ما رأيك يا تيان
Don't you think
هل تشعرين
this photo is full of love?
‫هذه الصورة مليئة بالحب‬
Assistant Tang.
المساعد تانغ
Where's Assistant Tian?
أين المساعد تيان
She hasn't come back
قالت للتو بعد أن ذهبت إلى الحمام
after she said that she went to the bathroom.
لم تعد بعد
Senior.
أيها الزميل الأكبر
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
The event is over.
انتهى النشاط
Sit.
اجلس
Senior.
أيها الزميل الأكبر
You were the one
هذه المرة الخيرية
who led this charity.
من الواضح أنك أنت من قام بذلك
Why are you hiding here
لماذا تختبئين هنا
during the interview?
تختبئين هنا سرا
Let me ask you.
أسألك
A wandering house
منزل ضال
saving the stray babies.
لإنقاذ طفلة ضائعة
Did we achieve the goal?
هل حققت هدفك؟
Then, to me,
بالنسبة لي
that is enough.
هذا يكفي
The most important thing
العمل الخيري
is the result.
‫هي النتيجة‬
What I learned from senior
تعلمت ذلك مع الزميل الأكبر
is never just the surface.
‫ليس فقط من السطح‬
Come on, baby.
هيا يا صغيرتي
I saw a pendant
رأيت قلادة
which is very similar to the hidden logo in your illustration.
‫تشبه العلامة المخفية في لوحتك
So,
لذلك
I give it to you.
أهديها لك
Thank you
شكرا لك هذه المرة
for helping me this time.
على مساعدتك
Senior, you...
أيها الزميل الأكبر أنت
You know the hidden logo in my illustration?
أنت تعرف علامتي المخفية في رسمي
I read your previous works carefully.
قرأت عملك السابق بعناية
It's very amazing
يمكنني تجميع اسمي والعلامة بشكل مثالي
to combine your own name with the logo.
‫هذا مذهل‬
Actually, not many people can see it.
‫في الواقع من النادر أن يعرف‬
Senior is really amazing.
‫الزميل المتقدم حقا رائع‬
Thank you senior.
‫شكراً لك أيها الموجه‬
Tian.
تيان
What?
ماذا
I need to talk to you.
أنا أبحث عنك
Sorry, senior.
أنا آسف أيها الزميل الأكبر
I have to excuse for a while.
سأغادر
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل
What are you doing, Mr. Liu?
ماذا تفعل سيد ليو
You're being weird
هذا غريب جداً
and rude!
غير مهذب
I'm rude?
أنا غير مهذب
Luo Ci
مثل لو سي
almost touches your face with his hand.
سيلمس يدك
But he is considered as polite.
إنه مهذب
It's not what you thought just now.
لم يكن الأمر كما تظنين قبل قليل
No.
ليس هكذا
Then what?
ماذا تعني
Tian, I…
تيان أنا
Mr. Liu, it's late.
المدير ليو الوقت متأخر
I'm tired. I'll go back first.
أنا متعب، سأعود الآن
Gosh.
يا إلهي
It's the wrong way again.
لقد عكس الطريق مرة أخرى
I'm not finished yet.
لم أنتهي بعد
Luo Ci's hand almost touched her face.
يد لوه سي على وشك لمس وجهها
I just restated the scene of the accident.
لقد عدت إلى موقع الحادث فقط
Why did she run away?
لماذا هربت
Mr. Liu.
المدير ليو
So who touched Assistant Tian's face?
إذا من لمس وجه مساعدة تيان
Me, of course.
بالطبع أنا
Then, that's different.
هذا مختلف
Mr. Liu, you're really flirting without people realizing.
سيد ليو أنت حقاً مغازلة بلا شكل
Now I have the reason to believe that
لدي سبب الآن لأصدق
Both of your loves are two-sided
أن السهم في الحب متجهان
Think about it.
فكر
Assistant Tian has such a big reaction
إن مساعد تيان
towards your touch.
ردة فعلها قوية جدا
Doesn't it just prove that
ألا يثبت أنك في قلبها
you are special in her heart?
في قلبها؟
But why did she avoid
لكن لماذا تختبئ
my flirting affection?
أنا مغرورة جدا
Girls should be reserved, shouldn't they?
يجب أن تكون الفتاة متواضعة
Maybe she's very excited internally.
ربما تكون متحمسة جدا
You're right.
أنت على حق
Tian must be shy.
يجب أن تكون دان خجولة
I knew it.
كما قلت
How could he fall in love with Luo Ci
كيف لي أن أعجبك
after meeting someone as excellent as me?
كيف لي أن أحب لوه سي؟
Yes.
نعم
Mr. Liu,
سيد ليو
I've informed Curator Fang
لقد أخبرت المدرب "فانغ"
to give Assistant Tian two movie tickets
لأشكرك
to show his gratitude.
تذكرتين فيلم إلى مساعدة تيان
It is a love movie.
فيلم الحب
If everything goes well,
إذا لم يحدث شيء غير متوقع
Assistant Tian will ask you out tomorrow.
مساعد تيان سوف يدعوك غدا
Well done.
أحسنت هذه المرة
You made up for your mistake.
سأعوضك عن أخطائك
Time to go home.
انتهى العمل
Beautiful! A two-sided love!
‫جميلة، انطلق إلى الجانبين‬
Unbelievable.
لا أصدق
I'm back to life.
إعادة إحياء الدماء
♫As long as you give me an affirmative look♫ (Bonus Scene)
طالما عينيك تؤكد
♫My love would become meaningful♫
الحب له معنى
meaning... (Bonus Scene)
معنى